Toni Morrison Papers, 1917-2015: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Writings, 1917-2015; 66 boxes
  - Subseries 1A: Novels, 1917-2015; 1970-2015; 66 boxes
    - Jazz, 1917-1992; 1989-1992; 10 boxes
      - Chapter 1, circa 1989-1992; 2 folders
        - Violet Revised, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 4)
          Pages 1-5.
        - Violet Revised, 1989 June 23; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 4)
          Pages 1-6.
        - Violet Revised, 1989 July 11; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 4)
          Pages 1-7.
        - Violet Revised, 1989 July 11; Printout. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 4)
          Pages 1-11.
        - Jchap 1: Violet Revised, 1989 August 19; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 4)
        - Violet X: Violet Revised, 1989 December 25; Printout. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 4)
        - Jchap 1 [formally Violet Revised], 1990 September 23; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 4)
          Pages 1-20.
        - Jchap 1 [formally Violet Revised], 1990 October 16; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 4)
        - Jopen, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - Jopen, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - Jchap 1 [formally Violet Revised], 1991 January 19; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-25.
        - Jchap 1 [formally Violet Revised], 1991 January 19; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - Chapter 1, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-27.
        - Chapter 1, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-29.
        - Chapter 1, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-30.
        - "Daylight slants like a razor...", circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-9.
        - "Besides, sth, I know that woman.", circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 2, circa 1989-1992; portions of 2 boxes
        - Annotated Folder, circa 1989-1992; 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Joe/Dorcus, June 26 no year; Printout. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Joe/Dorcus, June 26 no year; Printout. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-8.
        - Joe/Dorcus, June 26 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-8 and inserts.
        - Malvonne, 1990 July 5; Printout. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Malvonne, 1990 July 5; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 2, 1990 July 19; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 2, 1990 October 16; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 2, 1990 October 16; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 2, 1991 January 20; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-33.
        - Chapter 2, 1991 January 20; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - "Or used to...", 1990 July 5; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 1)
          Pages 31-63.
      - Chapter 3, circa 1989-1992; 2 folders
        - Annotated Folder, circa 1989-1992; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Dorcus, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Dorcus, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Dorcus, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Dorcus, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-12.
        - Dorcus, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - "Toward the end of February...", circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
          2 pp.
        - Alice Manfred, 1989 July 11; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
          Page 1.
        - JChapter 3: Alice and Dorcus, 1990 July 30; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - JChapter 3: Alice and Dorcus, 1990 July 30; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - JChap 3: Alice and Dorcus, 1990 July 30; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-14 and inserts.
        - JChap 3: Alice and Dorcus, 1990 October; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-21.
        - JChap 3: Alice and Dorcus, 1990 October 31; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - JChap 3A, December 3 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Notes:Jchap 3 or ?, December 3 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
          Pages 2-11.
        - JChap 3A, 1991 January 6; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - JChap 3A, 1991 January 18; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - JChap 3A, 1991 January 18; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
          Pages 1-17.
        - JChap 3: Alice and Dorcus, 1991 January 21; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - JChap 3A, 1991 February 22; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - JChap 3A, 1991 February 22; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
          Pages 1-18.
        - Rev. Insert Jchap 3A, February 22 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - 3, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - "If I remember right...", circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
          Page 26.
        - Chapter 3, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
          Pages 26-41.
        - Chapter 3, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
          Pages 26-42.
        - "If I remember right...", circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
          Page 90.
      - Chapter 4, circa 1989-1992; 2 folders
        - Annotated Folder, circa 1989-1992; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Vio/2, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Vio/2, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Vio/2, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Violet/2 revised, 1989 July 13; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Chapter 5, 1990 July 22; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
          Pages 1-19.
        - Draft: Jazz; Violet, 1990 July 23; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
          Pages 1-13.
        - Chapter 5/Change to Chap 4, 1990 September 23; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Chapter 5/Jchap4, 1990 November 23; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Chapter 5/JChap4, 1991 January 21; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Chapter 5/Jchap4, 1991 January 21; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 4)
          Pages 1-26.
        - Chapter 5/Jchap4, 1991 January 21; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-31.
        - Chapter 5/JChap4, 1991 February 24; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-34.
        - Chapter 4, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-35.
        - Chapter 4, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 5, circa 1989-1992; 1 folder
        - Annotated Folder, circa 1989-1992; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - Joe Trace, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - Jazzorg2, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
          Page 4.
        - "Blue music and white flowers...", circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - "To see if we can write on this machine...", circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-10.
        - Joe ms 1, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - JChap4/Change to Chap 5, 1990 October; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-15.
        - JChap 5, 1990 November 2; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - JChap 5, 1990 November 7; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-14.
        - JChap 5, 1990 November 30; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-12 and inserts.
        - JChap 5, 1991 January 9; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 5, 1991 January 21; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 5, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-22.
        - Chapter 5, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-24.
        - Chapter 5, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
          Page 18.
        - Chapter 5, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - Chapter 5, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 6, circa 1989-1992; 2 folders
        - Annotated Folder, circa 1989-1992; 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Golden, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Golden, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Golden, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Golden, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - "where he used to be and might be still.", circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
          Pages 2-5.
        - "sodden with liquid rage...", circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
          Pages 7-9.
        - Violet/3 re: Golden Gray, 1989 July 14; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
          Pages 6-11.
        - Violet/3 re: Golden Gray, 1989 July 14; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Violet/3 re: Golden Gray, 1989 July 14; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - JChap6: Golden Gray, 1990 Summer; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - JChap6: Golden Gray, 1990 September 28; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - JChap6: Golden Gray, 1990 October 9; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - JChap6: Golden Gray, 1990 November 25; Printout (photocopy). 1 item (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - JChap6: Golden Gray, 1990 November 25; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 7, circa 1989-1992; 2 folders
        - Annotated Folder, circa 1989-1992; 1 item (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - Hunter, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - "mother's distraction...", circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 3)
          Pages 15-19.
        - JChap 7, 1990 October; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - JChap 7, 1990 October; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - JChap 7, 1990 November 2; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - JChap 7, 1990 November 20; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 3)
          Pages 1-16.
        - JChap 7, 1991 January 20; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 3)
          Pages 1-23.
        - JChap 7, 1991 January 20; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - Chapter 7, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - Chapter 7, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - Chapter 7, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - J. Inserts, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - "picked chickens and cotton...", circa 1989-1992; 1 item (Box 24, Folder 4)
          Page 225.
      - Chapter 8, circa 1989-1992; 1 folder
        - Annotated Folder, circa 1989-1992; 1 item (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - Jvoice 2, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - JChap 8, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - JChap 8, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - JChap 8, 1991 February 1; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - JChap 8, 1991 February 1; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - Chapter 8, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 5)
          Pages 228-235.
      - Chapter 9, circa 1989-1992; 1 folder
        - Annotated Folder, circa 1989-1992; 1 item (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Jchap9, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Jchap9, 1991 January 30; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Jchap9, 1991 March 11; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - J additions, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 10, circa 1989-1992; 1 folder
        - Jazz End, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Jazz End, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Jazz End Rev., circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Jazz End Last Version, 1989 June 5; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Replace Jazz End, 1989 June 26; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Replace Jazz End, 1989 June 26; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 July 5; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 July 12; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 November 21; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 December 30; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 December 30; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 December 30; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Replace Jazz End, 1991 January 19; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 10, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 10, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Chapter 10, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Jazz Drafts, circa 1989-1992; 3 boxes (1 partial)
        - Jazz Draft, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 8)
        - Jazz Draft, 1990 October 16; Printout (photocopy), corrected. 1 item (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - Jazz Draft, 1990; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
          Pages 1-284.
        - Jazz Draft, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
          Pages 1-285.
        - Jazz Draft, circa 1989-1992; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
          Pages 31-285.
        - Jazz Draft, circa 1989-1992; Printout (photocopy). 1 item (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
        - Jazz Draft, circa 1989-1992; Printout. 1 item (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
        - Jazz Draft, circa 1989-1992; Printout (photocopy). 1 item (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
          Pages v-285.
        - Jazz Draft, 1992; Printout (photocopy). 1 item (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
      - Jazz Setting Copy, 1991; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
        Pages b, i-vii, 1-284.
      - Jazz Sample Pages, 1991 October 22; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Jazz First Pass Proofs Master Set, 1991 November 18; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
        Pages A-B, i-viii, 1-225.
      - Jazz First Pass Proofs, 1991 November 18; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
        Pages i-viii, 1-225.
      - Jazz Second Pass Proofs Master Set, 1991 December 19; 1 item
        - Jazz Second Pass Proofs Master Set Pages A-B, i-viii, 3-114 (formerly 1-112)., 1991 December 19; 1 item (Box 27, Folder 8)
        - Jazz Second Pass Proofs Master Set Pages 115 (formerly 113)-230., 1991 December 19; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Jazz Second Pass Proofs, 1991 December 19; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
        Pages A-B, i-viii, 1-227.
      - Jazz Third Pass Proofs, 1992 February 4-17; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
        Pages A-B, i-viii, 1-228.
      - Jazz Cut Proofs, 1992 February 4; 1 item (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
      - Jazz Knopf Canada Proof Pages, 1992 February-March; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Jazz F&Gs, 1992 March 19; 1 item (Box 29, Folder 1)
        Pages 1-[229].
      - Jazz Blueline Proofs, 1992; 1 item (Box 29, Folder 2)
        Pages [1]-229.
      - Jazz Advance Copy, 1992; 1 item (Box 29, Folder 3)
        Pages [1]-[226].
      - Jazz Production Mock-up, 1992; 1 item (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Paradise, 1971-2014; 1992-2014; 11 boxes
      - Paradise Research Files, 1971-2013; 2 boxes
        Consists of research notes, photographs, and photocopies of articles, book excerpts, and primary sources.
        - Brazil, undated; 3 folders (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
        - Gibson, Arrell Morgan: Oklahoma: A History of Five Centuries, 1981; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - Historical Atlas of Oklahoma, 1986; 1 item (Box 30, Folder 5)
          Photocopied book, published by the University of Oklahoma Press.
        - Miscellaneous, circa 1992-1995; 2 folders (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
          Includes correspondence from David Carrasco, Rachel Harding, Cheryl Townsend Gilkes, Lois Brooks, and others.
        - Nicodemus, undated; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - Oklahoma, circa 1994-1999; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 2)
        - The Oklahoma Story, 1978; 1 item (Box 31, Folder 3)
        - Photographs, 1996; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 4)
        - Schwendemann, Glen: Nicodemus: Negro Haven on the Solomon, 1971 June; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 5)
          Photocopied document, published by the State of Kansas Commission on Civil Rights.
        - Soil Survey Series, 1995; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - Research for 2014 Introduction, 2013; 2 folders (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
      - Outlines and Notes, circa 1994-1997; 2 folders (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
      - "Fleetwood", undated; Notepad pages. 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - "They shoot the white girl first...", undated; Notepad pages. 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - "3rd Chapel", undated; Notepad pages. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - "He looked back...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - "Green persimmon", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - "1963/Soane's abortion...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - "In the deepest part of the cellar...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - "1. Soane and Dovey...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - "Some must see in order to believe...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - "Feelings/Friendship w/ Soane..", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - "1. 'Pity' for what she sees in Pallas' womb...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - "1. Accident in front of Convent...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - "Color Coded instances", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - "O Holy Night", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - "No doubt about it...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 2)
        Includes notes for "On the Backs of Blacks."
      - "Sweetie wouldn't discuss it...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - "She had no (driver's) license...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - "K.D. wears the dashiki and Pro-Keds", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - "Grace 1970", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - "via K.D.", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - "Brow", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - "Chap. 4 Cont'd", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - "She said 'Where will you bury them?'", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - "Too early for cellar", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - "To New Mexico with Guy...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - "When chasing dreams...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - "Patricia/Did not try...", undated; Notepad. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - War, undated; Printouts. 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - The Bake Oven, undated; Printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Ruby, circa 1994-1997; 2 folders
        - "They shoot the white girl first...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 17)
          Pages 1-[3].
        - "They shoot the white girl first...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - "They shoot the white girl first...", circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - "They shoot the white girl first...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - Chapter One and Chapter Two, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 17)
          Pages 1-23, 12-13.
        - Ruby, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - Ruby, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - Ruby, circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 17)
          Pages 2-18.
        - Ruby, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - Ruby, circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - Ruby, circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - Ruby, 1994 August 12; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - Ruby, 1994 August 15; Printout. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - Ruby, 1994 August 24; Printout. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - Ruby, 1994 December 8; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
          Pages 2-24.
        - Ruby, circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - Ruby, circa 1994-1997; Printout (photocopy), corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - Ruby, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - "dream he is in might go...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
          Page 6.
        - "dream he is in might go...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Mavis, circa 1994-1997; 2 folders
        - Mavis Notes, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Mavis, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - "'Okay. But what I want to ask...'", circa 1994-1997; Printout. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 1)
          Pages 4-8.
        - Mavis, circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Mavis, 1994 July 29; Printout. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Mavis, 1994 August 15; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Mavis, 1994 August 16; Printout. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Mavis, 1994 August 26; Printout. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Mavis, 1994 August 26; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - Mavis, 1994 August 26; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - Mavis, 1994 December 8; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - "sink tap and peeled away the sticker.", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 2)
          Pages 69-71.
        - Chapter 2: Mavis, July 5 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 2)
          Pages 27-78.
      - Grace, 1994 August 18-September 6; 1 folder
        - Grace, 1994 August 18; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - Grace, 1994 August 26; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - "The train slowed...", 1994 September 6; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 3)
          Pages 23-25.
        - "from her joint...", circa 1994-1997; Printout, corrected; and handwritten page. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 3)
          Pages 31 and 33, with addition.
        - Grace, 1994 August 26; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - Grace, 1994 August 26; Printout, corrected (photocopy). 1 item (Box 34, Folder 3)